Good news, everyone.
You all know the orphanarium
where Leela grew up.
- Sure. We talk about it all the time.
- Really?
No. Burn!
Well done, fellows.
Anyway, said orphanarium
has named Leela "Orphan of the Year."
Your parents must be so proud.
- Ooh, sorry.
- And the good news keeps on coming.
Behold, my latest invention.
Neat.
Ta-da! It's a glow-in-the-dark nose
you can wear over
your regular non-glowing nose.
Observe.
Whoa! Clool!
Now I can punch you in the nose
in the dark.
Where'd it go?
Hey, Professor, what's all this groop
blurking out of the machine?
That? It's, uh, nothing. Yes, nothing.
If you think it's anything,
you're a suspicious moron.
It looks like toxic waste.
And it smells like toxic waste.
What does it taste like?
Delicious fig pudding! Ooh, that's good.
But a distinct aftertaste of toxic waste.
All right, all right! So the machine
produces a few toxic by-products.
You don't have to make
a federal case out of it.
I'm afraid I do.
I order you to dispose of that toxic waste
properly or bribe me.
Either way, it'll cost $500.
Five hundred real dollars?
That's an outrage!
Professor, I'll take care of that waste
for $499 and 100 cents.
Hmm. I know that's a rip,
but I'll pay for the convenience.
- Do you take credit cards?
- Let's find out.
All right, environment.
You've met your match.
Hey, get back in the sewer, weirdie.
No mutants on the surface.
But he ruined my wedding dress.
Honey, that thing was ruined
the minute it went on you.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
You know, it's not easy being an orphan.
Not if I have anything to do with it.
Oh, God!
But today's honoree, Turanga Leela,
has really made something of herself.
I'll never forget the night
that cute little alien baby
was abandoned on our doorstep.
Because I have a photographic memory,
and I remember every night.
What the... An alien language.
I guess you're an alien.
What a beautiful,
gigantic eye you have...
Well, come on in.
From those humble beginnings,
Leela went on to become
a county certified starship captain.
And so it is my pleasure today,
to nail her picture
alongside those
of our most distinguished alumni.
Thank you very much. Like many of you,
- I never knew my parents.
- Give me a...
I don't know...
- ...if they were alien overlords...
- That little...
...or simply underpaid alien janitors,
- who fought crime on the side.
- There we are. Picture's up.
It's crooked!
In the end, though,
it doesn't matter who my parents were.
All that matters is what I learned here,
within these unscalable walls,
that I had the strength
to make it on my own.
Just like all of you kids here today.
Leela! Leela! Leela!
Look at me! I'm Leela!
Nuh-uh, 'cause I'm Double Leela.
Whee!
That's it, Albert.
No more espresso for you.
Mind if we get a picture of you
with your picture for the news, ma'am?
Yes. I mean, no.
Just make sure you get my nonchalant side.
Whoo!
If those aren't tears of happiness,
please stop crying.
It's okay, Fry. I'm fine.
I won an award today.
Is it this room that's making you sad?
It's probably the room.
Come on. Let's go for a walk.
I'm sorry you saw that, Fry.
I usually try to keep my sadness
pent up inside,
where it can fester quietly
as a mental illness.
Yeah, I do that with my stupidness.
I told a whole crowd today
that being an orphan made me strong.
But all I really wanted was a mom and dad
to hold me and stroke my hair
and tell me they love me.
Then today's your lucky day,
because I happen to be a holding,
stroking, lovin' machine, also spanking.
That's not even close
to what I had in mind.
Well, anyway, just remember
that people care about you.
I know.
Sometimes, when I'm lonely,
I look up at the sky,
and I get this feeling
that somewhere, on some unknown planet
circling a distant star,
my parents are up there,
looking down on me.
Yo, yo, Ba-zender, what up?
My dumping business is booming.
I just got hired to clean up
the set of Free Willy 3.
Bender, cut it out!
First of all,
the sewer mutants will be mad.
Second, everything else that's
horribly wrong with what you're doing.
Eh, those stupid mutants
can't do anything.
You seem to be forgetting one simple fact.
Namely, I'm up here,
and they are safely down...
What did I do to deserve this?
Behold, our once-beautiful
mutagenic sewage lake.
The radioactive waste you've dumped in it
has made it bright enough
to see how ugly we really are.
Oh, man!
As if our lives
weren't miserable enough already.
- Tell me about it.
- Let the punishment commence!
- Punishment?
- No fair!
Bender's innocent!
The instant you touch
these mutateous waters,
your DNA will be forever altered,
turning you into horrible mutants like us.
- Especially him.
- Oh!
Allow me to demonstrate.
Ew!
It's like that time
I peeked in the kitchen at Imperial Hunan.
Submerge the prisoners!
Wait. I don't even have DNA.
Why am I screaming?
We're gonna beat you afterwards.
Oh, God!
Mutate! Mutate! Mutate!
Turanga Leela!
Who said that?
How do you know my real name?
Whee!
What happened?
I don't know. I think I saved us somehow.
Go after them!
The waters can't mutate us mutants!
Duh, duh, duh!
They went this way!
Quick! In there!
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Great Cheech's ghost!
What's this junk?
It looks like...
a timeline of my whole life.
That's when we saved Earth
from a giant asteroid of garbage.
And here's when I dropped out
and bummed around India for a while.
And this is just last year
at Space Mardi Gras.
It's like some kind of weird Leela museum.
And I'm the Leela.
Dude, over here!
It's all the best stuff
I ever flushed down the toilet.
Those are some of my diary pages.
And my screenplay!
And also, for some reason, the letter
I wrote you full of my personal feelings.
Oh, I'm scared!
My whole life has just been a show
for some perverted mutant.
- They must be here.
- Capture them!
And then, Bender ran.
Leela, freak out later.
We're not done escaping yet.
Got ya!
- Take this!
- Ow!
This time I'm calling
for the death penalty.
And not just because I'm running
for reelection as supreme mutant.
Four more years!
Psst!
Oh, very well. Your attention.
Instead of being tortured to death,
the prisoners shall hereby be expelled
from the sewers
and never allowed to return.
Oh, cruel fate!
Can we really never return
to this dank pit of sewage?
Wait a minute.
Why aren't you gonna kill us anymore?
Yeah, what are you, chicken?
Shut up, you two.
We can kill ourselves when we get home.
They'll need transportation
to the surface.
Bring in the airship.
- Ew!
- We constructed it from the remnants
of old discarded Macy's Parade balloons.
Underdog's groin,
Bart Simpson's left ear and right shin,
Garfield's owner Jon's forehead.
Fire up the sewer gas!
Move it, you ugly normals!
Whoa!
Huh?
I'm getting dizzy. I can't walk straight.
Whoa. Whoa!
Come on, Leela. You can do it!
Hurry, we're missing our bus!
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm gettin' on the bus!
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
They know something about me.
And I've got to find out what.
The lake didn't mutate me.
What is going on here?
It worked for me. I used to be
a little blonde girl named Virginia.
Who the hell are you?
No one. And watch your language,
young lady!
Stop right there!
I don't wanna hurt you.
I didn't want you
to hurt me either.
Leela's going nuts, and I can't save her
unless I learn more
about her mysterious past.
Isn't there anything else you can tell me?
Nah. Nothing that wouldn't be
a waste of your time.
That's impossible,
because my time is worthless.
Oh. Well, then there is one thing.
It's the note I found with Leela
the day she was abandoned.
But it's written in Alienese,
so no one on Earth can translate it.
- Not even Brainzilla.
- Hand it over.
Sure.
I just wish I could be more helpful.
Would you like some dirt
on any other orphans?
Look. I'm trying to save someone here.
I'll have to come back for those later.
- Can you translate it?
- Of course.
But only into Beta-crypt-three.
A language so complex, there's even
less chance of understanding it.
I didn't ask for
a completely reasonable excuse.
I asked you to get busy.
Very well.
Isn't that the same machine
that makes noses?
It can do other things. Why shouldn't it?
Of course, even if it is possible
to analyze the message,
there's no way of knowing
how long it would take.
It could take an hour,
or it could take a hundred million years.
Is it done?
Certainly not. Two dings means it's done.
But not like that. Slightly more rapid.
Where did they go?
Good news, Leela. I landed the contract
to empty all the spittoons
in Little Italy.
Ew!
That's it. It's done.
I can't believe it. My mind is boggling.
The analysis of the note
is printing out now.
It's a girl.
My God, she's beautiful.
No extra anythings.
What people skills!
She's completely perfect!
In my professional opinion as
an ear, ear, ear, nose and throat doctor,
she is the least mutated mutant ever born.
And yet, she's cursed to live
the horrible, degrading life of a mutant.
Like all of us. Especially him.
It's true.
Maybe we can do better for her.
I made this bracelet so that in some
small way, we'll always be with you.
Even when it doesn't seem like it.
During your entire life,
for example.
You won't pass for human, cutie.
But if my PhD in Excel-Linguistics
is worth diddly-poop,
this note should convince them
you're an alien.
And that'll be enough
to give you a real life.
- She'll never know we're her parents.
- That's our gift to her.
Better we should die than have her learn
the shameful truth of her origin.
I'm with ya.
I guess you're an alien.
What a beautiful,
gigantic eye you have...
Well, come on in.
Keep quiet so she doesn't hear us.
- What's there to talk about?
- Shh!
Hands up!
- Tentacles too!
- Don't say anything stupid, Morris.
What is all this?
Am I a game to you?
Or some kind of
even more boring Truman Show?
Do you believe I'm your Messiah?
The mutant Dalai Lama?
Stop me if I guess it.
- Well, actually, they're...
- Morris, shh!
And what about this?
Where'd you get this bracelet?
Did you steal it from me
when I was a baby?
Or from my parents?
You robbed my parents, didn't you?
I bet you sick mutants killed them!
My parents were confused aliens
lost on Earth, and you killed them!
Is that it? Admit it!
Yes, we killed them.
You guessed the truth.
Because of you,
I'll never know my parents!
I'll kill you!
That would be best.
Stop!
Thanks, Bender.
Don't do it, Leela!
- They killed my parents!
- Close.
- They are my parents.
- Yes.
I had the professor analyze the Alienese
letter that was found with you.
- What does it say?
- I dunno.
But the analysis showed
it was printed on recycled toilet paper.
A squeezably soft paper
used mainly in the sewers.
It says,
"Your parents love you very much."
We still do.
So, I'm not an alien? I'm a mutant?
We never wanted you to know.
You deserved a better life.
You must despise us.
You're my parents!
All I've ever wanted is to know you.
This is the happiest moment
of my life.
Aw!
When I see you alone
I see what's in your mind
You want me
Yes, you do
You don't need to tell me
I know you love me most
No one else take my place
You need me
Yes, you do
Forever and ever
When we kiss
I see what's in your heart
You love me
Yes, you do
You don't need to tell me
I know you love me most
No one else take my place
You need me, you do
Forever and ever
We are
Baby love child
I'll take you so high
Groovy love child
Give me a kiss
Baby love child
Do it again